

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a full-stack web developer with experience in back-end and front-end development.

My background includes developing web applications from scratch, including back-end and front-end. I participated in development of ERPs, APIs, websites, trading bots and chart generators. Possessing excellent communication, project management, teamworking and leadership skills with logical and problem solving thinking.

# **CONTACT**

LINKEDIN: www.linkedin.com/in/endreujvari

E-MAIL: ujvendre@gmail.com

## **LANGUAGES:**

English (Full Professional) Hungarian (Native or Bilingual)

## **CERTIFICATIONS AND COURSES:**

- The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp
- Angular The Complete Guide (2022 Edition)
- Asynchronous Programming in .NET Core
- Build an app with ASPNET Core and Angular from scratch
- The Ultimate MySQL Bootcamp: Go from SQL Beginner to Expert

# ENDRE ÚJVÁRI

## FREELANCE FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Freelance Software Developer

November 2021 - Present

- Development of trading bots which make market orders automatically on different stock and crypto exchanges.
- Development of exchange market analyzer software which identifies the best circumstances to make a market order based on given parameters.

## Random Capital Zrt Software Engineer

November 2019 - October 2021

 Developed trading platforms for stock exchange, ERP of the company, and designed database.

## Raab-Prog Kft. PLC Software Engineer

April 2019 - October 2019

• Worked on PLC programming and automation of factory lines.

# Clarus Software Kft. Software Engineer

September 2018 - January 2019

Created ERP of the company.

# **EDUCATION**

## University of Szeged Bachelor of Science – BSc. Molecular Bionics Engineering 2012 - 2019

## **SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE**

